<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learning Android</string>
    <string name="button_label_toast">Toast</string>
    <string name="button_label_count">Count</string>
    <string name="count_initial_value">0</string>
    <string name="toast_message">Hello Toast!</string>
    <string name="article_title">Activities</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">From Android Developer Guide</string>
    <string name="article_text">An <b>activity</b> is the entry point for interacting with the user. It represents a single screen with a user interface. For example, an email app might have one activity that shows a list of new emails, another activity to compose an email, and another activity for reading emails. Although the activities work together to form a cohesive user experience in the email app, each one is independent of the others. As such, a different app can start any one of these activities if the email app allows it. For example, a camera app can start the activity in the email app that composes new mail to allow the user to share a picture. An activity facilitates the following key interactions between system and app.
        \n\n<i>- Keeping track of what the user currently cares about (what is on screen) to ensure that the system keeps running the process that is hosting the activity.
        \n\n- Knowing that previously used processes contain things the user may return to (stopped activities), and thus more highly prioritize keeping those processes around.
        \n\n- Helping the app handle having its process killed so the user can return to activities with their previous state restored.
        \n\n- Providing a way for apps to implement user flows between each other, and for the system to coordinate these flows. (The most classic example here being share.)
        \n\n</i>You implement an activity as a subclass of the Activity class. For more information about the Activity class, see https://developer.android.com/guide/components/activities .
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_template_basic">TemplateBasicActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
</resources>

